forumshawaii.net 2014-04-08

# Privacy Policy - FH Classifieds

Register now to gain access to all of our features. Once registered and logged in, you will be able to create a ad, post replies to existing ads and threads, give reputation to your fellow members, get your own private messenger, post status updates, manage your profile and so much more. WE ONLY ALLOW HAWAII RESIDENTS ON FH CLASSIFIEDS TO POST ADS. Your account will be deleted if you do not have a Hawaii IP address. This message will be removed once you have signed in.  

**Privacy Policy Sharing your information**  
We do not share, sell or lend your information to any one for marketing purposes.  
We do not employ tracking devices for marketing purposes.

**We collect**  
We do collect your email address, for purposes of sending confirmation emails, authenticating your account.  
We may disclose information about our users to law enforcement officers when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or to protect the safety of our users and the Public.

**Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site**  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to our web site or the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites, which have a link on our Website, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Your Consent**  
By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.

**Data we store**  
We make good faith efforts to store the information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security.

  1.
